Guide to the Harold and Joyce Pomeroy Schwartz Public Art Archive 1961-2009 (bulk 1976-2005) MSS.171
Fales Library and Special Collections
Harold and Joyce Pomeroy Schwartz Public Art Archive
1961-2009
1976-2006
Fales Library and Special Collections
Schwartz, Joyce Pomeroy
MSS.171
70 Linear Feet
The Harold and Joyce Pomeroy Schwartz Public Art Archive documents the work of public arts administrator and consultant Joyce Pomeroy Schwartz. The collection consists of Schwartz's professional records, pertaining to her involvement with Pace Gallery and Works of Art for Public Spaces, Ltd. This collection includes artist biographies, invitations and exhibition information, photographic materials, reviews and promotional materials, professional correspondence, administrative files, financial records, contracts, and project proposals.
Biographical Note
Joyce Pomeroy Schwartz grew up in Brooklyn, New York. She received her BA in English Literature and American History from Hunter College, and her MA in Art Education at New York University. Soon after, Schwartz became involved in both the political and art scenes in New York City, sparking her interest in art in a public context.
In 1967, Schwartz opened and managed a gallery specializing in fine art photography called "The Photographer's Gallery" until its closing in 1971. In 1979, she helped found ArtTable, a group of women dedicated to talking about the role of women in the art world. From 1973 to 1981, she worked as the Director of Commissions at Pace Gallery, developing programs in public art and architecture.
In 1982, Schwartz became the president of Works of Art for Public Spaces Ltd., a consulting firm in contemporary art focusing on architecture and landscape. Schwartz continued to direct the firm, curate exhibitions and write critically about public art.
Joyce Pomeroy Schwartz died on December 2, 2025.
Bibliography: http://www.marciagyerman.com/pdf/marciagyerman.com-joyce-pomeroy-schwartz.pdf http://www.linkedin.com/pub/joyce-pomeroy-schwartz/6/5a3/21a
Scope and Content
The Harold and Joyce Pomeroy Schwartz Public Art Archive consists of the professional records of Joyce Pomeroy Schwartz, pertaining to her involvement with Pace Gallery and Works of Art for Public Spaces, Ltd.
The collection spans from 1961 to 2009, covering her career as an artist, director at Pace, and president of Works of Art for Public Spaces, Ltd. Much of the material coincides with Schwartz's work as the Director of Commissions at Pace, where she started to focus on developing public art with artists in New York City. Works of Art for Public Spaces, Ltd., a consulting firm in contemporary art, continues to combine art in architecture and the public sphere in several cities across the country and abroad. This collection documents the work of Joyce Pomeroy Schwartz as an artist and art critic, as well as a commissioner and consultant for major art organizations.
The collection includes artist biographies, invitations and exhibition information, photographs and slides, reviews and promotional materials, professional correspondence, administrative files, financial records, contracts, and project proposals.
Further scope and content description is found at the beginning of each series.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Missing Title
Series I: Artists Files includes artist biographies, photographic materials, invitations, promotional materials, exhibition information, and reviews. This series is arranged alphabetically by artist's last name.
Series II: Administrative Files includes personal and professional correspondence, contracts, financial records, and project proposals. This series is arranged alphabetically by artist's last name, project title, or location.
Series III: Data Storage includes digital portfolios and other electronic media, and is arranged alphabetically by artist's last name.
Series IV: Video includes supplemental audiovisual material and minimal audio material from both artists and organizations. It is arranged alphabetically by last name or, in the absence of a name, by title.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to researchers. Appointments are necessary for the use of manuscript and archival Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.collections.
Provenance
The Harold and Joyce Pomeroy Schwartz Public Art Archive was donated to NYU's Fales Library and Special Collections in two batches, in 2005 and 2009.
Related Material at Fales Library and Special Collections
A.I.R. Gallery Archive (MSS.184)
Andrea Callard Papers (MSS.156)
Annina Nosei Gallery Papers (MSS.298)
Artists Space Archive (MSS.291)
Creative Time Archive (MSS.179)
Exit Art Archive (MSS.343)
Fashion Moda Archive (MSS.091)
Group Material Archive (MSS.215)
New Museum Library Lucy Lippard Collection (MSS.169)
Public Art Fund Archive (MSS.270)
REPOhistory Archive (MSS.113)
Separated Materials
The books that were donated with this collection will be catalogued and made available in the NYU Libraries catalog at a later date.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Born-digital and audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
High Line (New York, N.Y.: Park); Art and society.; Art criticism.; Artists -- New York (State) -- New York -- Exhibitions; Art -- Exhibitions.; Exhibition catalogs.; blueprints (reprographic copies); Financial records; Files.; Posters.; Invitations.; Reviews (document genre); Public sculpture, American |v Exhibitions.; Announcements.; Architectural drawings (visual works); Installations (Art) -- United States.; Administrative records; Photographs.; Slides (photographs); Acconci, Vito, 1940-; Aycock, Alice; Public Art Fund (New York, N.Y.); Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum; Sugarman, George, 1912-1999; Stuart, Michelle, 1933-; Denes, Agnes; Ferrara, Jackie; Highstein, Jene, 1942-2013; Kozloff, Joyce; Madsen, Loren Wakefield; Neri, Manuel, 1930-; Poirier, Anne; Poirier, Patrick; Ross, Charles; Sculpture Center (New York, N.Y.)
- Series I: Artists Files
  Scope and Content
  Series I: Artists Files represents Schwartz's subject files for individual artists. The files include artist biographies, photographic materials, invitations, promotional materials, exhibition information, and reviews. This series is arranged alphabetically by artist's last name. When Schwartz had multiple files for a single artist, those files were retained rather than being combined.
  Separated Materials
  Compact disks in this series were removed to Series III: Data Storage.
  - Abakanowicz, Magdelena, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abakanowicz, Magdelena - Slides (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abakanowicz, Magdelena - Invitations, Bio, Exhibition Info, Etc., 2005 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abrams-Collens, Vivien - Photos/Slides, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Abrams-Collens, Vivien - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Acconci, Vito - Slides [1 of 2], 1983-1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Acconci, Vito - Slides [2 of 2], 1977-1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Acconci, Vito - Slides, Press, Etc. [1 of 10], undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Acconci, Vito - Postcards/Slides [2 of 10], undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Acconci, Vito - Slides, Press [3 of 10], undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Acconci, Vito - "Proposal Drawing", Slides [4 of 10], undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Acconci, Vito - Photos, Slides [5 of 10], undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Acconci, Vito - CD [6 of 10], undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Acconci, Vito - "Resume/Bios" [7 of 10], undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Acconci, Vito - "Pink Playground" [8 of 10], undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Acconci, Vito - Photos, Slides, Press, Etc. [9 of 10], undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Acconci, Vito - "Coca-Cola" [10 of 10], undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Acconci, Vito - "MoMA Exhibition" [1 of 5], undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Acconci, Vito - "Acconci's Writing" [2 of 5], undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Acconci, Vito - "House of Cars" [3 of 5], undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Acconci, Vito - "Acconci Reviews" [4 of 5], undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Acconci, Vito - "Copies of Written Proposals" [5 of 5], undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Acconci, Vito - "Misc. Correspondence" [1 of 3], undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Acconci, Vito - "Acconci Articles" [2 of 3], undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Acconci, Vito - "Acconci Visuals" [3 of 3], undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Aceru, Raul - Slides, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Adams, Alice, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Adams, Alice - Slides, 1977-1995 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Adams, Alice - Invitiations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Adams, Alice - Reviews, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Adams, Alice - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Adams, Dennis - Slides, 1983-1992 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Adams, Dennis - Invitations, Bios, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Adams, Dennis - Photos/Slides, 1992-2000 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Adams, Dennis - Reviews, 1986-1999 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Adams, Mac - Slides, 1983-1995 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Adams, Mac - Invitations, Bio, 1987-1995 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Adams, Phoebe, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Africano, Nicolas - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1976-1996 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Africano, Nicolas - Reviews, 1979-1995 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Africano, Nicolas - Photos/Slides, 1989-1996 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Aheary, John - Slides, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Ahreus, Hanno - Slides, 1984-1989 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Aitken, Doug - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Aitken, Doug - Photos/Slides (Catherine Chalmers?), 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Aitken, Doug - Reviews, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Akakce, Haluk - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2003 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Albenda, Ricci - Reviews, 1997-2001 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Albenda, Ricci - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Abenda, Ricci - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Albuquerque, Lita [1 of 4] (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Albuquerque, Lita [2 of 4], undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Albuquerque, Lita [3 of 4], undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Albuquerque, Lita (CD) [4 of 4], undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Albuquerque, Lita [Kotobuki Corporation] [Tochigi] [1 of 4], undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Albuquerque, Lita [Kotobuki Corporation] [Tochigi] [2 of 4], undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Albuquerque, Lita [Kotobuki Corporation] [Tochigi] [3 of 4], undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Albuquerque, Lita [Kotobuki Corporation] [Tochigi] [4 of 4], undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Albuquerque, Lita - "Contract/Invoices" [Kotobuki Corporation] [Tochigi], undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Alexander, Clytie - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1996 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Alexander, Clytie - Photos/Slides, 1991-1996 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Alexander, Clytie - Reviews, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Terry, Allen - Invitation, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1966-1994 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Terry, Allen - Reviews, 1986-1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Terry, Allen - Photos/Slides, 1986-1994 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Alstine, John Van, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Alvarado-Juarez, Francillo, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Alys, Francis - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2002-2006 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Amore, B., undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Amores, Grimanesa - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2006 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Anderson, Gene - Invitation, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Anderson, Gene - Reviews, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Anderson, Jim - Photos/Slides, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Anderson, Jim - Reviews, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Anderson, Jim - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Andre, Carl - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2006 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Andre, Carl, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Antonakos, Stephen [1 of 3], undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Antonakos, Stephen [2 of 3], undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Antonakos, Stephen [3 of 3], undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Antonakos, Stephen, 1964-1994 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Antonakos, Stephen, 1973-1995 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Antoni, Jaine - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2003, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Anusziewicz, Richard - Photos/Slides, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Apfelbaum, Polly - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1978-2004 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Apfelbaum, Polly - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Apfelbaum, Polly - Reviews, 1990-2005 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Appel, Karen - Photos/Slides, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Aptekar, Ken - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Aptekar, Ken - Photos/Slides, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Aptekar, Ken - Reviews, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Armajani, Siah, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Armajani, Siah - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Armajani, Siah - Reviews, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Armajani, Siah - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Arman, Armand, 1964-1995 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Arman (Armand Pierre Ferandez) - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2000-2005 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Arman (Armand Pierre Ferandez) - Reviews, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Arman, Armand [1 of 4], undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Arman, Armand [2 of 4], undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Arman, Armand [3 of 4], undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Arman, Armand [4 of 4], undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Armleder, John - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2006 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Arp, Jean, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Artemis, Maria, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Artswhager, Richard - Photos/Slides, 1968-1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Artshwager, Richard - Reviews, 1974-1986 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Artshwager, Richard - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1983-1988 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Attie, Shimon - Photos/Slides, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Attie, Shimon - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1998 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Attie, Shimon - Reviews, 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Aubrey, Daniel - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Aubrey, Daniel - Reviews, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Aycock, Alice, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Aycock, Alice (Aycock A.I.A.) [1 of 4], undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Aycock, Alice [2 of 4], undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Aycock, Alice (Bio) [3 of 4], undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Aycock, Alice (Storm King Exhibition) [4 of 4], undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Aycock, Alice - Slides, Photos, Catalog [1 of 5], undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Aycock, Alice - "Aycock Proposals [2 of 5], undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Aycock, Alice - "Aycock Proposals [3 of 5], undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Aycock, Alice - Slides, Press [4 of 5], undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Aycock, Alice - Photos, Bios, Correspondence, Etc. [5 of 5], undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Aycock, Alice - Slides, 1979-1996 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Aycock, Alice [1 of 3], undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Aycock, Alice - Photos [2 of 3], undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Aycock, Alice - "Photos" [3 of 3] (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Aycock, Alice - Photos, [CDs], undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Aycock, Alice - JFK, undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Aycock, Alice, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Aycock, Alice - Aycock Correspondence, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Aycock, Alice - Aycock Bio, undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Azaceta, Luis - Invitations, Bio, Exhibition Info, Etc., 1999 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Azara, Nancy - Invitations, Bio, Exhibition Info, Etc., 2004 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Baca, Susan, Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2006 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Baechler, Donald - Photos/Slides, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Baechler, Donald - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1999 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Bagley, Frances - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1997 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Baikenhol, Stephen - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1996 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Baikenhol, Stephen - Reviews, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Baldessari, John - Photos/Slides, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Baldessari, John - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1999 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Bamberger, Tom - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2002 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Baraneck, Frida - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2003 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Baraneck, Frida, Photos/Slides, 1985-2003 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Barney, Matthew - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2006 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Barr, David, undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Barry, Judith - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1978-2000 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Barry, Judith - Photos/Slides, 1982-1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Barry, Judith - Reviews, 1980-1991 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Barry, Judith - Proposals, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Bartlett, Jennifer, [1979-1992] (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Bartlett, Jennifer - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1992-1997 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Bartlett, Jennifer - Photos/Slides, 1990-2001 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bartlett, Jennifer - Reviews, 1982-2006 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Basquiat, Jean Michel - Photos/Slides, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Basquiat, Jean Michel - Reviews, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Basquiat, Jean Michel - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2006 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Basu, Jyothi - Reviews, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Batcheller, Edward, 1983-1990 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Batcheller, Edward, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Baumgarten, Lothar - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Baumgarten, Lothar - Slides/Photos, 1983-1988 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Baumgarten, Lothar - Reviews, 1981-1993 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Beal, Jack - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2001 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Bearden, Romare, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Bearden, Romare, 1979-1994 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Bearden MTA, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Bearden, Romare - Subway, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 20a)
  - Beasley, Bruce - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1997 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Begheyn, Claire, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Behar, Roberto & Rosario Marquardt - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2003 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Behar, Roberto & Rosario Marquardt - Reviews, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Belcher, Alan, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Belge, Harrington, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Bell, Larry, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Bell, Larry - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1962-2006 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Bell, Larry - Reviews, 1982-1996 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Bell, Mercedes, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Bell, Roberley - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Bell, Roberley - Proposals, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Beu Tre, Howard, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Benedit, Luis, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Benedit, Luis - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Benedit, Luis - Reviews, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Benglis, Lynda - Photos/Slides, 1983-1998 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Benglis, Lynda - Reviews, 1984-1996 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Benglis, Lynda - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Benglis, Lynda - Proposals, undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Benglis, Lynda, undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Bennet, Gordon, undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Berg, Eric - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Berg, Eric - Reviews, 1993-1998 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Berlant, Tony - Photos/Slides, 1977-2003 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Berlant, Tony - Reviews, 1985-2003 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Berlant, Tony - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1993-2003 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Berlant, Tony, undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Berlyn, Sheldon - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1997 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Berne, Michelle, undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Berwick, Rachel - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc. (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Berwick, Rachel - Photos/Slides, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Berwick, Rachel - Reviews, 1993-1998 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Bevilacgua, Michael, undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Bessemer, Linda - Photos/Slides, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Bessemer, Linda - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Bickerton, Ashley, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Bickerton, Ashley - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Bickerton, Ashley - Reviews, undated (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Biederman, Jim, 1980-1983 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Biggs, Janet - Reviews, 1990-1994 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Biggs, Janet - Photos/Slides, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Biggs, Janet - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1995-2004 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Billian, Cathey, undated (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Bills, Tom, 1983-1995 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Bills, Tom - Reviews, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Bills, Tom - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Bing, Xu - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2003 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Bischton, Ginny - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Bischton, Ginny - Photos/Slides, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Bischton, Ginny - Reviews, 1995-2005 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Bishop Good, Francie - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Bishop Good, Francie - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Bishop Good, Francie - Reviews, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Blackburn, Jean - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Blackburn, Jean - Photos/Slides, 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Blackburn, Jean, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Bladen, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Bladen, Ronald, 1963-1987 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Bloom, Barbara, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Blue, China, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Blum, Andrea, 1980-1995 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Blum, Andrea - "Correspondence", undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Blum, Andrea - "Bio", undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Blum, Andrea, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Bochner, Mel, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Bochner, Mel, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Boepple, Willard - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1996 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Bolande, Jennifer, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Boltanski, Christian, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Bon, Lauren Ariel, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Bontecou, Lee - Press, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Booker, Chakaia [1 of 2], undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Booker, Chakaia, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Borofsky, Jonathan, 1982-1995 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Borofsky, Jonathan [1 of 2], undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Borofsky, Jonathan [2 of 2], undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Boroson, Lee, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Bosman, Richard, 1982-1987 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Botero, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Botero, Fernando, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Bourgeois, Louise, undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Bourger, Marie, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Bowen, Nancy, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Bowen, Nancy - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1995 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Bowen, Nancy - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Bowen, Nancy - Reviews, 1990-1994 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Boynton, Peter, undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Braden, Bill, undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Bradshaw, Dove, undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Brettville, Sheila di - Slides, undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Bronson, A. A., undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Brooks, Adam, undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Brown, Carol, undated (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Brown, Carol - CD, undated (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Brown, Deborah - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1990-1995 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Brown, Deborah - Reviews, undated (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Bruguera, Tania, undated (Box 5, Folder 54)